<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Networking</string>
    <string name="overview">Overview:</string>
    <string name="play_to_film">Choose film</string>
    <string name="click_me">Сlick me</string>

    <string-array name="images">
        <item> https://www.themoviedb.org/t/p/w1280/chTkFGToW5bsyw3hgLAe4S5Gt3.jpg </item>
        <item> https://www.themoviedb.org/t/p/w1280/ygPTrycbMSFDc5zUpy4K5ZZtQSC.jpg </item>
        <item> https://www.themoviedb.org/t/p/w1280/nFjYv60aOwqrGSGYPPIP8yXOxm3.jpg </item>
        <item> https://www.themoviedb.org/t/p/w1280/wcG47dkutXa3FG9gYqvnVp51p1P.jpg </item>
        <item> https://www.themoviedb.org/t/p/w1280/pStgVcVSMNDykydPzMTuAiXAb50.jpg </item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="overview">
        <item> Ex-cop James Malone is serving a life sentence for a crime he didn’t commit.
               He is offered a chance at freedom if he can survive a deadly game of Apex, in which
               six hunters pay for the pleasure of hunting another human on a remote island.
               He accepts, and once he arrives, all hell breaks loose. </item>
        <item> The charming dog Clifford lives in an ordinary family. Thanks to boundless love and
               care, the little red puppy has grown to gigantic proportions. An unusual creature
               immediately attracts the attention of a greedy corporation that has planned something
               very evil. Together with his two-legged friends,
               Clifford must thwart their insidious plans. </item>
        <item> Marie, HR manager of a small company, is forced to receive Gabriel, his new assistant.
               She does not like him. Why does he make her life a living hell? What if a secret
               united them? Did Gabriel know her in the past? </item>
        <item> With her deadline fast approaching, Mimi the cat panics across the vast halls of a
               tech company on a mission to gain approval from her uncaring superiors. </item>
        <item> Los Angeles in 2045. A policeman and his robotic partner enter a forbidden enclave
               inhabited by people affected by an unknown disease. Together, the heroes discover
               the real cause of the disease and do everything to stop it. </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="titles">
        <item> Apex </item>
        <item> Clifford </item>
        <item> Sigma </item>
        <item> Good Job </item>
        <item> Android Cop </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="vote_average">
        <item> 5.6/10 </item>
        <item> 8/10 </item>
        <item> 10/10 </item>
        <item> 8/10 </item>
        <item> 4.2/10 </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
